- That's the last of the load?
- Yup.
Alright. We're good!
- Ho-ho.
- Hey, Joe, I'm on a break.
Break, huh?
Yeah. You ever heard
of one of those?
No.
Storm's coming.
Take the load in the morning.
Stay in town tonight.
No man, I'll be all right.
I gotta be back by tomorrow
and take care of some shit.
Okay.
- You got chains?
- Yeah, I got chains.
If you get caught, you make sure
you chain up for S-curves.
What is this, orientation?
I got it.
Besides, if it gets
a little gnarly on the pass,
I'll just bunk at your cabin.
You leave now, you'll make it.
You stay the fuck away
from my cabin.
Drive safe, partner.
Always do, man.
Hey!
Dad! How'd you know
I was up here?
'Cause the birds told me,
that's why.
They started chirping 'cause
I was too close to their nest.
Mwah.
They tell you
that was coming, huh?
- Full moon.
- No, no, no, no, don't!
Stop!
- Did you miss me, babe?
- Yeah.
It's been like
three whole days.
It was five days, honey.
Charlotte get her.
Save Mom!
Stop!
Get off of me.
No, don't you dare!
You better give me kisses.
Give me a kiss.
Soup's on the stove.
Come here. Give me a kiss.
Mwah.
See you tonight.
Okay.
I'll see you tonight.
If you're even up
by the time I get home,
- I'll consider that foreplay.
- Uh-oh, what is that?
I don't know
what she's talking about.
Where's your grandpa?
Oh, putting up Christmas lights.
Back there.
Oh, yeah, Christmas lights.
That was a real adventure.
He's in the garage.
Good luck with that.
All right.
You go make me some soup.
Charlotte, you want
a little brother?
Mrs. Braven, see you tonight.
Yeah.
Ha ha ha!
When I get home, Joe Braven,
when I get home...
I love you.
Hey, Pops.
Hey.
What are you doing?
I came out here
to find something.
Christmas lights.
Right here, Dad.
Oh. I thought they'd...
Well, they should be up here.
Put things
in their proper place.
You always put things
where they're supposed to be.
I'm working on it. Cheers.
What is this?
It's a porter.
Tastes like a shit milk shake.
Dinner's ready. Let's go.
Daddy?
Yeah.
You were asleep again.
- No.
- Uh-huh.
- Uh-huh?
- Yeah.
You calling me a liar?
- Stop!
- Huh?
You always fall asleep.
That's 'cause
it's time for bed.
There's Piggy.
But you didn't even
finish the story.
- Really?
- Yes, really.
All right, where were we?
"The forest animals
play hide and seek.
Bethany Bear hides in her cave.
She falls asleep,
and her friends can't find her.
Winter turns to spring.
And she's crowned the best
hide and seek champion
in the whole forest."
The end.
Boop.
Stop!
Good night, pig.
Don't do that again.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
Oh, I finished
Grandpa's bracelet.
Can I give it to him?
He's probably asleep, honey,
just like you should be.
We'll give it to him tomorrow.
Turn the light out.
I love you.
Pops?
Oh, Jesus, not again.
Hey, Pops.
Hello?
Joe, hey, it's Mike
from the Trinity Bar.
Yeah, listen,
you better get over here.
Yeah, your dad's here again.
Excuse me?
Time for us to go home.
Let go.
- Come on, baby.
- I don't...
Hey!
- Joe!
- I got it.
I'm on my way.
Linden, no!
Hey, what's going on?
Dad's at the Trinity again.
- I'll be back.
- Okay.
You okay?
No, no, I understand.
Yeah, I understand.
Okay, thanks, Harris.
Guy he got into it with is on
parole for aggravated assault,
so he doesn't want
to press charges, but...
we got a problem, Joe.
It kills me to see
your father this way,
but this happens again,
I'm gonna have to arrest him.
And you too.
Yeah, I got it.
We finished stitching him up
'cause it was a head injury.
Daddy!
Hello, pumpkin.
Daddy, what happened
to your face?
I was wrestling with Grandpa.
- How's he doing?
- We finished stitching him up.
- Go check on Grandpa, okay?
- Okay.
'Cause it was a head injury,
I ordered the MRI.
- How's it look?
- It looked okay,
but how'd he get in a fight?
He thought a woman at the bar
was his wife.
It was my fault. I was
supposed to be watching him.
Is he alone
when you two are at work?
I mean, I schedule my lessons
to work around Joe being gone,
but sometimes things come up.
Well, since your father's
accident last year,
his mental condition
is getting worse.
Let me talk to another
neurologist, okay?
- He'll do a complete scan.
- No, we're done with that.
Then I suggest you consider
a much more supervised approach.
I'm not putting my dad
in the home.
Look, that's not
the only option.
Is he ready to go?
Just think about it, Joe.
Yeah.
All right, baby girl.
Let's get you home,
get you to bed.
Okay.
Bye, Dad.
- See you at home.
- Yeah.
That's, uh...
Donny's girl.
Right?
That's Charlotte, Dad.
That's your granddaughter.
Yeah, yeah, that's right.
Yeah, Charlotte, yeah.
Let's get you home, Pops, hmm?
You ready motherfucker, hmm?
Hey.
Don't you puss out on me, man.
So how often do you make
this run up north again?
About every two weeks.
Okay, any other drivers
that make this run?
We're not gonna involve
anyone else, man.
Why the fuck not? That's how
you branch out, move up.
There ain't nobody else you can
trust to bring on this deal?
It's not about trust, man.
I'm just not
involving anyone else.
That's why you're always
gonna stay a fucking runner.
That's fine, man.
I'm just gonna collect my money.
Hold on!
What the fuck?!
Jesus Christ.
What the fuck, man?
Damn it.
What the fuck?
Oh, Jesus Christ.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
All you had to do was drive
the fucking truck, man!
We gotta get this shit
out of here
before somebody comes, man.
Fuck. Go get my bag
and the ax.
Fuck!
- Where is it?
- Right here, right here.
Give me the fucking flashlight.
- Right here?
- Crack that fucker open.
There you go.
- That's my truck, man!
- Holy shit.
That's my fucking truck!
Relax.
Open the fucking log.
Dude, just get back here.
Hurry up.
Jesus, that's a lotta dope.
I know. Kinda makes you hard,
don't it?
Come on.
Load the fucking bag up.
- Here, take it out of the bag.
- Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Fuck. We need to
extinguish this, man.
We gotta get rid of the dope
before the cops come.
Just get it in the bag.
Dude, just figure out
where we're gonna go.
All right.
We're not too far
from my boss' cabin.
It's a couple miles up the road.
We'll stash it there.
All right, let's go.
Honey, what are you doing?
It's almost
one in the morning.
I'm almost done.
Go back inside.
Joe.
Look at me.
Hey.
I don't wanna put my dad
in a home.
He's the strongest man
I've ever known.
Now look at him.
I don't want Charlotte
seeing him like that.
I know.
But we're a family.
Okay?
And we will
make it through this.
Maybe this doesn't have
to be our decision alone.
You can talk to your dad.
Take him to the cabin.
Just you and him.
You know he loves it there.
Just get the conversation
started.
Hey.
- All right, this is it.
- Thank God.
You sure it's good here?
Yeah. Joe's not
coming up here, man.
Oh, fuck.
All right.
Come on, man,
hurry up.
It's cold as shit up here.
Here.
All right, good, man.
We'll pick it up tomorrow.
Fuck.
Dude, I'm freezing.
Just fucking take it
if you're fucking cold.
Dude, I'm trying
to share with you.
Take the fucking blanket, man.
Stay here.
Thank God.
Shit.
It's okay. Relax.
Don't worry about.
Thank you, sir!
You stupid motherfucker.
This is really funny
to you, huh?
That shit on the side
of the road, that's my life.
You should be worried
about Kassen.
I gotta make the call,
so shut the fuck up about it.
What's up, Kassen?
Are you hungry?
Pancakes here ain't half bad.
Look, I know that I fucked up,
but I'll make
this thing right.
Please give me the chance.
Fuck.
What?
Slight hiccup.
I don't have it with me.
Oh, no.
But I got the whole load.
Check this out, man.
I know you wanted me to spread
this out over several runs,
but I got this whole
motherfucking thing in one trip.
Genius.
Where is it?
It's over the border, man.
We got it stashed.
It's all good.
Slight hiccup is that
we flipped the truck,
and the cops came.
I got my boy Pete
coming after it.
Don't worry about it.
It's all good, all right?
You tell Pete to stay home.
- I'm coming.
- You can't smoke that in here.
- I'll get him to put it out.
- Where the fuck are you?
- It's okay.
- Some fucking shitty hotel.
- Sir!
- It's okay, ma'am. I got it.
Where we at, Weston?
Greenwood Inn, room eight.
We're at the Greenwood Inn,
room eight.
Fuck.
Put it out, dickhead.
Dickhead.
This is gonna hurt.
Morning.
Hey, Dad.
Morning, Grandpa.
Hey!
Look at you.
- Hey, you make that for me?
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Hey, Pop, how you feeling today?
I'm good. I feel good.
Hey, I'm feeling like
I'm ready to go back to work.
I think you need to take
the day off, Dad, okay?
I was thinking maybe
we'd go up to the cabin.
Cabin? What for?
Well, you can help me
shut it down for the winter.
That's the first time
your old man
ever asked for my help
with anything.
All right, I'll go.
I wanna go. Please?
Hey, I'll take you hunting.
Maybe I can fix
one of those bad habits
you're picking up
from your dad.
You know what? Actually,
I don't have to work today,
so I need your help
around here.
Oh, Mommy, please?
Don't give me that look.
No, ma'am.
Don't look at me.
Dad, I never see you.
Charlotte, listen to me.
I owe you, okay, baby?
I promise I'll take you
next time.
You always say that.
She's yours.
Listen, I got everything
packed up,
so you wanna
grab your stuff?
All right. You mind
if I eat an egg first?
I'll drive.
I got it, Pops, I got it.
All right.
Get comfy, old man.
Shit.
Ah.
- Hey.
Goddamn! You get off
on this shit, huh?
Nice G.I. Joe gear, boy.
Who's your friend?
This is Weston, man.
He's gonna lead the way.
Okay.
Why don't you
ride with Gentry?
You can ride with us, Weston.
Gentlemen!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, easy, man.
Hey, what's up, man?
How you doing?
Good.
We got power.
We'll get those curtains open,
let some light in.
Somebody left the crib
half empty.
Wanna bring in some timber?
Yep.
There you go.
Can I talk to you
for a second, Dad?
Why don't you get
the coffee going?
Yeah, yeah, just a minute.
Can I ask you something?
You remember what happened
last night at the bar?
I had a disagreement,
wound up with 11 stitches.
Yeah, I remember.
You grabbed a woman by the arm
and tried to pull her out.
They said you thought
she was Mom.
Nah. I don't think so.
Do you remember seeing
Charlotte at the hospital?
Hey, what is this, huh?
What are you doing?
What are these questions?
The doctor thinks you need
a different kind of supervision.
I need to be supervised?
No, but when you go off
and do stuff that...
What else does the doctor think?
I need to be put somewhere,
maybe put in a home, huh?
No, we're not
doing that, okay?
But we gotta talk about
something else that we can do.
Oh, we do, huh?
Let me tell you something.
When my old man
gave me the mill,
he didn't have to because
he could still get it done,
and so could I.
I didn't put him out to pasture.
I didn't put him
in some goddamn home
with a bunch of drooling,
bedwetting old bastards.
I'm not gonna
put you in a home.
You're goddamn right
you're not!
Pops...
Yeah.
I forget some things now,
all right?
Hey, why don't you try
falling 40 feet
with nothing
but a helicopter dash
to break your fall?
See how you wind up, huh?
Hot shot.
Pops, I don't wanna fight.
I just wanna talk.
Yeah?
Is it working out the way
you thought it would?
Goddamn it.
Shit.
Stop right here.
Ah, shit.
Uh, I think, uh...
I think Joe
might be up here, man.
Dude, what the fuck
are you talking about?
You said the bag
would be safe.
All right.
Any other roads out of here?
No, this is the only one.
There's ATV trails
that go to the back ravines
and Blue Mountain,
but this is the only road.
The cabin's about
a half-mile away.
Cell service?
Not up here.
Except for maybe up
on Blue Mountain.
All right, we're gonna secure
the road 150 yards out.
Clay, Louisi,
take the east side of the road.
Ridley, Essington,
you take the west of the road.
We're gonna flank him.
Gear up.
Yo, G.I. Joe,
let me get one of those.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Look, I know this guy.
Let me talk to him.
- What is this, man?
- Talk to him, motherfucker?
We just need to go back in there
and get our shit.
Anyone who hasn't royally
fucked up in the last 24 hours,
raise your hand.
Shut the fuck up
and do as you're told.
Hit it.
What the...
Latch is busted.
- What the hell is that?
- I don't know.
Yeah.
There's tracks out there.
Footprints...
...around here.
Hi, Daddy.
Charlotte, what are you
doing here?
Does your mother know
where you are?
I left her a note.
Were you in the back
of my truck?
- Yeah.
- Baby, you're a rascal.
Pops, let's go!
Is everyone in position?
Not yet.
Almost.
Dad, I'm sorry.
Get in the car.
Another male rides shotgun.
Take 'em both out.
What?
Something's not right.
Come on.
Baby, get down, get down.
No shot.
Let's move to the perimeter
of the cabin.
Essington,
take the back east corner.
Louisi, front east.
Ridley, you'll take
the front west.
And, Clay, take the rear west.
Let me know when
you're each in position.
Let's go.
You can ride
in the big boy's seat.
Fuck, man.
- Close the curtains, Pops.
- What's going on?
It's gonna be all right, baby.
It's gonna be all right.
Daddy?
It's gonna be okay,
baby, okay?
- The CB is in the shed.
- You good to shoot?
What do you think?
- Dad?
- It's gonna be okay, baby.
Grandpa and I gotta do
a few things, all right?
- I can help.
- Help by staying out of sight.
It is very important that
you do not open this door
unless it's for me, okay?
- Okay.
- All right, baby.
Get in there.
Okay, I love you.
Ehh.
Once you're in position,
check in.
Copy. Rear east.
I got rear west.
Copy. Front west.
Roger. Rear east.
Hold your positions
until the bag is secure.
This is Joe Braven up on
Blue Mountain. Does anyone copy?
This is Joe Braven on
Blue Mountain. Do you copy?
This is Fish and Game.
Go ahead, Joe.
This is Joe Braven.
Come on, man.
Why we standing around?
Give me a gun. I'll go in there
and get it myself.
Do you know this guy?
Yeah, man.
Tell me about him.
How many of them?
I make four, at least.
But you need to see this.
- Motherfucker.
- Yeah.
What are you gonna do?
- I'm gonna go talk to him.
- No, no.
With that amount of drugs,
they're not here to talk.
They're gonna size you up,
take you out, then come for us.
I got an idea.
Son of a bitch.
Hey, you know
what you're doing?
I think so, Pops.
Why don't you
go bring him out?
Look, his family's in there.
Let's just come back
for the shit, man.
Motherfucker's got our drugs.
Just bring him out.
He's coming out.
Louisi, Ridley,
come in from behind.
Well, look at you.
I'm so sorry, man.
Ah, Mr. Braven.
Sorry to interrupt your day.
Yeah.
Where the fuck's
the rest of it?
If you shoot me, my guys
will burn the other half.
Okay.
You clear off my property.
I'll meet you in town
at the Waverlin Cafe in an hour.
I'll bring the rest of it,
and you'll never see me again.
Oh, no, no, no, fuck that.
You get your Sasquatch ass
back in there
and bring all of it out now,
motherfucker.
No, Joe,
I don't wanna go into town.
A city boy like me
wouldn't be welcome there.
And besides, what if I run
into Stephanie or Charlotte?
I didn't come here
to kill good people.
I just want
what belongs to me.
Joe, just do
what they want and then...
So how 'bout you go inside,
get the rest of it,
and then we'll be on our way.
Could you do that for me, Joe?
Please?
Uh, yeah.
Watch him.
You know if you give
the other half,
we're as good as dead.
I got a sniper
in the front woods.
I'd like to take him out.
Not yet, Pops.
We gotta get Charlotte
out of here,
then I'll come back for you.
Until then, just wait.
Roger that.
Hi, baby. I got you.
You're doing so good.
Come on.
It's gonna be okay,
all right?
Soon Grandpa and I are gonna
need your help, all right?
- I'm ready.
- That's my tough little girl.
You stay right here.
I'll be right back.
You still got 'em?
Yeah, I do.
Wait for my signal.
Once we have
the other half secured,
take 'em all out.
Copy that.
Copy.
Yeah, yeah.
He's got the bag!
Fuck!
Goddamn it. You with me.
Lay down some cover.
Second floor.
God damn!
Nobody gets out of that cabin.
- Go!
- Oh, hell no!
Hey!
Hey, I need a fucking gun!
Fuck.
Charlotte,
you remember the plan?
- Okay.
- Yeah?
You get to the top,
you call Mama.
- Yeah.
- I love you.
Go.
Run, run.
Go!
Stop.
Kill the engine.
Wait.
The main road's that direction.
Why is he looping back around?
- Ah...
- What's going on?
He's not trying to run.
He's going back to the cabin.
I'm going uphill,
try to find a sniper position.
You push him back towards me.
Charlotte!
Charlotte, come on, baby.
Oh, shit!
All right.
He's down on
your side of the gorge.
Secure the bag,
clean him up.
I got the bag.
And where's Braven?
I'll find him.
Kassen, Joe didn't...
Gentry, say again.
Say again, Gentry.
Please pick up.
- Joe.
- Mom?
Charlotte?
Charlotte, you can't
run off like that.
Stop. Mom, there are men
shooting at us.
- What did you say?
- They're shooting.
I'll meet you
at the lookout boulder
on Blue Mountain.
Where are you? Hello?
Charlotte, baby,
I'm losing you.
Hello, hello?
If you'd like
to make a call...
Shit.
Sheriff Ossler.
Hey, Cal?
This is Stephanie Braven.
Listen, Joe's up at
Blue Mountain.
There seems to be
some sort of trouble.
- Trouble?
- Yeah.
Charlotte called and said
there were men shooting.
I don't know.
Anyway, she lost reception.
I tried calling her back,
and I can't get through.
All right,
we'll check it out.
- I'm headed up there right now.
- No, you're not.
We'll handle it.
Just hurry, please.
Dispatch, this is Ossler.
Deputy Harris and I
are headed over to Blue Mountain
to respond to a call.
Will advise when we arrive.
What's going on?
Shots fired over at
the Braven cabin. Let's go.
Man, look,
it's probably just some kids
who are shooting cans off
some fence posts or something.
Fuck you, man.
That's fucked.
Shit.
I think Joe's daughter
was in that cabin.
Ridley, get to the top
of the mountain.
Kid's trying to call for help.
- Essington.
- Copy.
Move to the west side
of the cabin.
Take a cover position.
Clay, take your position
near the back.
I get my hands on this bag,
we kill all these
sons of bitches.
Clay, bag was another decoy.
He's headed towards you.
You go east along the trail.
I'm coming.
We'll flank him.
Over.
I'm trying to find it.
Clay, find the ATV trail.
He's coming back on that.
The drugs are
still in the cabin.
Essington, Hallett,
hold the perimeter.
Do not engage.
Do not give him any excuse
to burn those drugs.
Goddamn it!
You fucking missed me!
Fuck!
I should just
fucking shoot him.
You dumb fucking Indian.
Whew!
Fuck.
Clay.
- Clay, you see him yet?
- Not yet.
- Come on.
- He's right there!
Come on!
Essington,
Joe's coming.
Move to the east side
of the cabin, near the trail.
See if you can't get
a clean shot on that sniper.
Take him out.
Goddamn bastard.
Fuck.
No!
Ah, fuck!
Pin him in!
Dad! Dad!
Dad, Dad, it's Joe.
Dad, it's Joe.
It's Joe.
Joe, Joe.
Dad, it's me.
Dad, you're Linden Braven.
You're Linden Braven.
I'm your son.
I'm your son. I'm your son.
Shh, Dad.
Come on!
We're getting out of here.
Come on.
Come on, Dad.
Come on, Pops.
All right.
That's it, Pops.
Come on, come on.
I got you. Here.
All right.
Sit down, sit down,
sit down.
Sit down, sit down.
Pops, look at me.
Look at me.
- I need you to wait here, okay?
- Okay.
- Stay here.
- I'll come with you.
All right, Pops,
I'll be right back.
- Joe.
- Stay here.
No!
Charlotte!
Charlotte, run!
Go to the road!
You take the side
and the front entrances.
I'll go around the back.
We're taking
this goddamn cabin now.
Fuck.
Hey, hey!
- Cal, stop. It's Charlotte.
- My mom and dad need help!
There are men
chasing my mom and dad.
- They're all over the cabin.
- Dispatch, this is 101.
Please send available units
to the Braven cabin,
Blue Mountain Pass.
Come on, Glen.
Braven!
Oh, shit.
Oh, oh, shit.
- Dad?
- Braven!
Dad?
Dad!
There he is.
Let him go.
Let him go!
Drop the ax!
Let him go.
You drop that fucking ax! [
Just let him go.
I'll go back inside,
get the bag, and you can go.
- Okay?
- You'll get my bag?
- Yeah.
- You gonna get my bag now?
I'm sorry.
That's what I wanted
in the first place!
Bring me another bag
of teddy bears? Fuck you!
Just let him go.
He doesn't know what's going on.
He's sick. Please.
Please just let him go.
Just let him go.
- You did this.
- Son, please.
You did this to him!
- No!
- Yeah!
- Old fuck!
- No!
Yeah!
Hey.
No, no, please no.
Fuck.
Son.
Dad.
No.
No, no.
Dad.
Pops.
No.
Oh, God.
Joe!
No.
This is Cal.
Shots fired at the Braven cabin.
Requesting immediate backup.
Joe!
101, this is 112.
Do you copy?
Another officer down.
Don't move!
Hands where I can...
Oh, baby, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Where's Charlotte?
I don't know.
I'll find her.
I think the cops are here.
Go around this trail. Get 'em.
- Go find our baby, all right?
- Yeah, of course.
- Joe, where's Dad?
- Go find her.
Okay.
Listen, EMS and Fire,
10-33, copy?
- We got EMS on the way.
- Ambulance is coming.
- Glen!
- Stephanie, get down!
Charlotte's in the car.
Go wait there.
- Mommy! Mommy!
- Baby, baby!
Baby, are you okay?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Let me...
Aw, Joe.
What the fuck's your problem?
Come on, fucker.
Come on!
Oh, I'll give it you.
You're a tough fucker, Joe.
I'll give you that.
What's going on, Joe?
You taking me
to step in this?
What is that?
Bear trap?
I'm gonna gut you, Joe.
I'm gonna gut your wife,
and I'm gonna gut
your little girl,
just like gutted
your old man.
Joe!
Daddy?
Daddy!
Charlotte!
- Daddy!
- Joe! Joe!
Oh, my God!
Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- Thank God.
Thank God you're okay.
Dad.
I'm okay, okay?
I was okay.